Contact

tejasjaggi007@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tejasjaggi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript
Project Management
Web Applications

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Limited Working)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Data Structures and Algorithms
Essential Guide To Entrepreneurship

Honors-Awards

Gold Stevie Winner School Whizkid Medal School Whizkid Medal

Tejas Jaggi

Software Engineer @ Cisco | ScoreMore Bengaluru

Summary

Having completed my B.Tech in Computer Science along with a minor in Business Management from Manipal Institute of Technology, Manipal, I am currently working as a Software Engineer at Cisco (Domain of Engineering and Supply Chain).

I had a short stint at HID Global where I worked on HID® SAFE™ and completed my industrial Training in the area of Product Development for their Physical Access Control Systems (PACS).

I have worked in the capacity of the Organising Committee Vice President for AIESEC in Manipal University for their annual event "Balkalakaar" and also held the position of a Business Development Manager for the organisation.

Experience

Cisco

2 years 8 months

Software Engineer I July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Bangalore

Program Manager, Men For Inclusion (India Chapter) July 2020 - Present (2 months)

Software Engineering Intern January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Founder

Score More

June 2020 - Present (3 months)

Manipal Institute of Technology

Computer Science & Engineering August 2014 - August 2018 (4 years 1 month)

Manipal, Karnataka

Quantum Secure, part of HID Global Product Development Intern May 2017 - July 2017 (3 months) Bengaluru Area, India

AIESEC

Organising Committee Vice President for Business Development October 2015 - October 2015 (1 month)

Manipal, Karnataka, India

Education

Manipal Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science | Minor in Business Management · (2014 - 2018)

Sanskriti School, New Delhi

High school, Science, PCM with Economics · (2008 - 2014)